JIM: Previously on Gotham...
ED: You have five
minutes, quiz kids.
Wayne Enterprises runs Indian
Hill, but who runs Wayne Enterprises?
FRANK: A weapon is en
route to destroy the city.
I can't take on Nygma and Barbara
and the rest of them by myself.
You said you want
to build an army, right?
What about an army of freaks?
Who ordered the
hit on my father?
Frank Gordon. Your uncle.
You have the right
to remain silent.
(GRUNTS)
Dock 9C. It's where the
weapon will be arriving.
Jim. Do I hear a
favor coming on?
- (MAN GRUNTING)
- What is coming into Dock 9C?
Now I know who I
am. I'm The Riddler.
It's good to see you, too.
How'd things go with Selina?
This is what I was made for.
The clone is in place.
Good evening, Alfred.
And to you, Master Bruce.
FRANK: You need to join
The Court of Owls, Jim.
A woman named
Kathryn is going to call.
He would have
been so proud of you.
No! (GASPS)
Kathryn, I presume.
I killed my uncle.
I make no apologies for it.
Maybe it's time we meet.
KATHRYN: My thought exactly.
(WIND HOWLING)
(BOTH PANTING)
Hello?
Anyone home?
When this guy gets home, we
gotta ask him to kick on the heat.
It's colder in here
than it is out there.
Fascinating.
I know you're hell-bent on
getting revenge on Nygma and all.
And forming an army
of freaks is a great plan.
- I mean, it was my idea, but...
- (SHUSHING)
Quiet.
I think I hear something.
Do you think it's him?
(GASPS)
Mr. Fries.
Welcome home.
(GROANING)
I see you still hold me responsible
for all of that awful monster rhetoric
I spewed during my campaign.
You ran people like
me out of Gotham.
We both know I
only said those things
because that's what the
voters wanted to hear.
Your experiments, Mr. Fries...
You're trying to reverse
your condition, aren't you?
I can help you.
Why would you do that?
My enemies took
everything from me.
Tried to murder me.
You help me get my revenge,
and when I take back my throne, I
will give you every resource you need
to free yourself
from this icy prison.
Even if I wanted to say yes,
I can only survive a few hours
outside the cold without my suit.
And you don't have it
because it's been locked away
in a Wayne Enterprises black site
ever since you
escaped Indian Hill.
- Ivy?
- Oh.
COBBLEPOT: Ta-da.
MR. FREEZE: My suit?
So, Mr. Fries...
Will you join us?
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
JIM: Where are we?
KATHRYN: Where we
are is not important, James.
What matters is why you're here.
- You know why I killed my uncle.
- Yes, I do.
Frank murdered your father.
What I need to know is if you
hold us accountable for his actions.
Frank acted alone.
He admitted as much to me.
Good.
Then we can proceed.
The city needs you now
more than ever, James.
There's turmoil ahead.
And good men like you are going
to be needed to hold it together.
But make no mistake,
The Court, and The Court
alone, can save Gotham.
So what do you want me to do?
Prove your loyalty to The Court.
Killing my uncle wasn't enough?
That was between you and Frank.
It had nothing to do with us.
When the time is right,
we will call upon you.
And Frank's body? It's
still in the brownstone.
We've already taken care of it.
(INDISTINCT POLICE
RADIO CHATTER)
- Who's the stiff?
- Jim's uncle, Frank Gordon.
- Never met him.
- They were estranged.
Have you seen Jim?
He's working a case.
Or he's walking in
the door as we speak.
Hey, Jim. Come in. We, uh,
have some bad news for you.
- What's going on?
- I'm sorry.
We found your uncle's
body this morning.
He was pulled out of the
harbor. I did my prelim.
The burns on his left temple
suggest he was shot at close range.
Lab is running ballistics.
You saw him at the
cemetery yesterday.
He seemed on edge.
Did he say anything?
No. He, uh, just stopped
by to pay his respects.
We didn't talk much.
Thanks, Lee. I'll
take it from here.
That's it? That's your reaction?
What do you want me to say?
I know you. You're
hiding something.
- You know something.
- BULLOCK: Lee, come on.
The man just lost his uncle.
Yeah, Harvey. You just
keep covering for him.
My condolences.
She's right. You do know
something, don't you?
Uncle Frank shot himself.
Said it was the only way
to get me inside The Court.
- Did it work?
- I met with a woman named Kathryn.
She says I have to prove
my loyalty to The Court first.
Look, I see the need
for playing it cool.
But right now, The Court's readying
a weapon that could destroy the city.
We don't have time to sit on
our thumbs and do nothing.
I don't like it any more than
you do, but if I push too hard,
we might blow the only
chance we have at stopping this.
And Uncle Frank
will have died in vain.
Okay. So what do we do now?
Kathryn said to get back to
work. Keep up appearances.
It shouldn't be too hard.
Look who resurfaced.
BARBARA: Hello?
Ed?
It's Barbara.
Your old friend you've
been blowing off.
I'll allow you to call me Ed
because we have history.
But my name
is The Riddler.
So the headlines say.
(CHUCKLES) Now,
why are you here?
When Penguin was mayor,
did he mention a
mysterious group?
One that controlled the
levers of power in Gotham
from the shadows
with total impunity?
- No.
- See, I didn't claw my way to the top
only to find out there's
someone above me.
I've been trying to
find out who they are,
but no one in this town seems
to know anything about them.
Then how is it that
you know about them?
Jim Gordon put me on to them.
And what is his
interest in all this?
He didn't say, but he
did ask me to investigate
a shipment coming
into Dock 9C yesterday.
The Harbormaster was
protecting a crate from Indian Hill.
- What was inside?
- I don't know.
Before I got a
chance to find out,
some masked assassin
slaughtered half my men.
What do you know?
When I was at Indian Hill,
Professor Strange hinted at
some powerful secret group,
but he didn't tell
me who they were.
This is the one
riddle that got away.
I will get you the
answer you seek.
But I will do it in my own way.
You're going to make a big
production of this, aren't you?
Only someone with power and connections
would have information on this group.
I need to speak
with Gotham's elite.
And nothing brings out the bourgeoisie
quite like opening night at the theater.
Where wilt thou lead me?
Speak, for I will go no further.
(AUDIENCE MURMURING
INDISTINCTLY)
I say, Ghost...
Speak your business
or I shall go no further.
ED: My business is not
with you, Prince of Denmark.
But with your audience.
(AUDIENCE MURMURING)
I've come to address you,
the ruling class of Gotham.
You've kept a
secret for far too long.
But tonight,
I will kidnap and torture one
of you to expose the truth.
So spread the word
to all your friends.
The Riddler is coming.
Also, I found your performance
to be wooden and unrealistic.
- (GROANS)
- (AUDIENCE GASPS)
And, scene.
And that, my old
mucker, is checkmate.
Good game, Alfred.
You let me win, didn't
you, Master Bruce?
- No way, Alfred.
- No way, my foot.
That's very
unlike you, isn't it?
And to be honest, I mean, you haven't been
yourself these past few days, have you?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I think you do know what
I'm talking about. So, come on.
Out with it.
The other day when I came home,
you asked how things
were with Selina.
I made it sound like
things were hopeful.
I lied.
She said she never
wanted to see me again.
I was embarrassed.
I was afraid you'd ask me
about seeing Selina, and I'd lie...
I just didn't want
to talk about it.
Well, I...
I understand, Master B.
And thank you very
much for being so candid.
And I really wouldn't
worry about Ms. Kyle.
You know, time has a way of
sorting these things out, doesn't it?
Talking of which, I
should check on the dinner.
- Alfred.
- Sir.
Thank you.
You're a good friend.
Glad to hear it, sir.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
It's me.
It's happening again.
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
Hey.
So, the audience has
been accounted for.
(SIGHS) Is this Hamlet?
I guess he wasn't meant to be.
You crossed paths
with Nygma recently.
Any idea what this secret
is he's talking about?
No, I have no clue.
My guess is he just made it up.
Captain, we got the all-clear.
All right.
This is all that's in there.
(CAMERA CLICKS IN BACKGROUND)
It's a riddle. Shocker.
Written in iambic pentameter.
Like a Shakespearean sonnet.
"I am a man who
holds a high position
"Who shows two faces
to all those he rules
"A fraud, criminal and
sometime politician
"Gotham, my
constituency of fools"
A two-faced politician whose
constituency is Gotham.
- The Mayor?
- Fraud. Criminal.
Sounds like he's describing Penguin,
but that doesn't make any sense.
Ed told Lucius
he killed Penguin.
Aubrey James. He was recently
reinstated, and he's been mayor before.
Sometime politician.
But why not just grab him?
Why tell us in advance?
Because Nygma wants to make a show
of it, and make us look bad in the process.
Call the Mayor's Office.
Tell them we're on our way.
We don't need Nygma for
anything. He should be dead by now.
He's obsessed with
finding the answer.
Which is an easy
solution for us.
Once he does, we'll
get rid of him. I promise.
And how's him causing a
scene at the theater help us?
It doesn't.
But it does help me more
fully announce myself
on the Gotham stage,
if you'll forgive the pun.
You wanna become
famous? Try dying.
- I can help you with that.
- Okay, that's enough.
What actually is your plan?
Kidnap Mayor James.
The man ran this
place for 10 years.
If anyone knows about this
mysterious group, he does.
You could've just said that.
I could've had him
here, being tortured.
Okay, see, but first I had to tell
the GCPD what I was going to do.
How else am I supposed to
properly embarrass them publicly?
My crimes must live up to my
name and this is no exception.
And what if the Mayor doesn't
know anything about this group, hmm?
- What then?
- I have a plan B to smoke them out.
But first, I need
something from you.
There's a biker bar on the
corner of Spaulding and 8th.
It's full of brawlers, lowlifes.
I need a bomb to
detonate there tonight.
I'll let you know when.
So tell us, genius, how do
you plan to get Aubrey James
now that you've told the
GCPD you're going after him?
Oh, that's simple.
They're gonna bring him to me.
You know how many crooked
politicians there are in this city?
This riddle could be for anyone.
Oh, my gosh, this is delicious.
All the same, Mr. Mayor, we'd like to
move you to a safe house, immediately.
Did you not see the
muscle twins over there?
I'm perfectly safe here.
Besides, what's The Riddler
want with me, anyway?
BULLOCK: We're not really sure.
He did say something to the
crowd at the theater about a secret.
My life's an open book.
You feeling okay,
Mr. Mayor? You look a little...
It's my blood sugar. I've had
too many of these danishes.
Where are my pills?
Wait a minute, where
did you get these?
An appreciative citizen. Why?
- Oh, boy.
- Nygma.
MAYOR JAMES: This is bad.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Yeah, I think I'll pass.
COBBLEPOT: You
cannot be serious.
I've seen mass graves
more inviting than this place.
Strange messed
me up pretty good.
He convinced me I was
some sort of goddess.
And it took me a
long time to get over it.
Now, this place might be
bad, but Gotham is worse.
Hey, freak. You're
on company time.
Get back to work.
IVY: You don't
have to take that.
- You should totally kick his ass.
- Yeah.
But he's my boss.
Bridgit, there is nothing
wrong with being a freak.
I'm a freak. So is Penguin.
You belong with us.
We've met before, haven't we?
Yeah. I'm Ivy
Pepper. Selina's friend.
Oh, I know. I ran into
one of Strange's puppies.
Kind of had a growth spurt. Though,
to be honest, I'm not complaining.
Ivy.
- And you're part of this?
- Yeah.
It's almost like we're a family.
You don't have to
be alone anymore.
I could kill your boss
just to sweeten the deal.
Nah.
- Hey, you. I quit.
- (GROANS)
(MAN SCREAMING)
Thank you for
letting me come in.
The nosebleeds
are getting worse.
You did the right
thing coming here.
- What did you tell Alfred?
- Nothing.
I said I was tired, then
snuck out of my room.
I'm dying, aren't I?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
The process that brought
you into this world was flawed.
Will I die before Bruce returns?
No. Bruce Wayne will be back
in Gotham well before then.
I know we've asked a lot of you.
After Indian Hill, I didn't know
what to do or where to go.
You gave me a purpose.
That's more than
most people can say.
I'm glad you see it that way.
When Bruce returns,
people are going
to die, aren't they?
A lot of people.
You haven't gotten attached
to anyone, have you?
Alfred, perhaps?
- You've spoken fondly of him.
- No.
I just want to know.
The number is immaterial.
What matters is that
Gotham must fall.
And because of
your sacrifice, it will.
Can we count on you?
Yes.
His BP's dropping. We
need to stabilize him.
I want this ER secured, badge
access only. No one gets in
- unless they're sick or dying.
- WOMAN: 10-4.
Nygma knows this is the closest
hospital to the Mayor's Office.
We brought him right to him.
Great. Let him show his face.
I got unis all over the place.
What are we missing, Harvey?
What could Aubrey James know
that's so important to Nygma?
ED: (OVER PA) Paging
Detective James Gordon.
Paging Detective James Gordon.
- Where's that coming from?
- Communications room. Second floor.
It's a trap.
- WOMAN: (OVER PA) Please, don't kill me!
- (GUNSHOTS)
Stay here.
ED: So, Jimbo. Now
you must be wondering
what I want from that
ding-dong Aubrey James.
Well, turns out, he
has answers to a riddle.
One that you put into motion when
you sent Barbara down to Dock 9C.
The question being,
who runs Gotham?
I gotta get out of here.
No, Mr. Mayor, you're in
no condition to go anywhere.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Jim, tell me you got him.
- He wasn't there.
But the secret he's
after, it's The Court.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- You better get back here, quick.
- What is it?
There was some
kind of explosion.
A lot of victims. I
got a bad feeling.
It's him. Don't leave
the Mayor's side.
- Authorized personnel only.
- To hell with that.
My friends got blown up.
(MEN GRUNTING)
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
Hello, Aubrey.
(MEN GRUNTING)
We got company.
Where is she?
Not here.
I know she and Nygma
kidnapped Mayor James.
Nygma mentioned Dock 9C,
and she's the only one I told.
Nygma's got a big mouth.
Wait, wait, wait. Let
me get this straight.
You mean this whole stupid
riddle thing with Nygma is real?
What? He clearly
knows everything already.
I heard a rumor he hurt
you pretty bad a while back.
Both of you. Surprised
you're defending him.
Listen, you tell
me where they are.
I'll take Nygma down,
but I'll get Barbara
a free pass.
It's true. I hate him.
But I don't know where they are.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
JIM: Harvey.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Nygma sent another riddle.
Never should have
brought Barbara into this.
You better hope
I get to her first.
You should've
given that freak up.
No one wants Nygma
dead more than me,
but I can't betray Barbara.
Yeah.
Cause she's always got
your best interest at heart.
Listen, you're in way
over your head on this one.
You don't want to
mess with these people.
You see, everything that you say
just makes me more
intrigued and determined.
I will be the one
who unmasks them.
MAYOR JAMES: You're insane.
Remember me, Aubrey?
I know that voice.
(WHISPERS) I'm so glad.
I thought maybe it got muffled
what with that box on your head.
(GIGGLES)
That was fun. We should do
that again for old times' sake.
You don't get it, do you?
These people, they're like God.
They see and hear everything.
They'll know I talked.
(GASPS) Then it's the box.
(STAMMERS) No.
Please, anything but that.
They call themselves The Court.
And?
That's all I know. I've
never met these people.
I just did what they
asked me to, I swear.
(CLAPPING)
Very good. Thank you, Mr. Mayor.
You've been very helpful.
Helpful?
All he gave us was "The Court."
He gave us tangible
evidence of their existence.
Now they'll know
I'm not bluffing.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to force The
Court to reveal themselves.
What is the one thing that every
secret organization is afraid of?
Being exposed.
Bingo.
Finally. Did you
bring what I asked for?
It's time to get The
Court's attention.
Baby.
Gordon came to the
club. He knows everything.
You should've never
gotten Nygma involved.
- I boosted the premium stuff, Otto.
- (MEOWING)
You're welcome.
BRUCE: Hello, Selina.
What the hell are
you doing here?
I wanted to see you.
I missed you.
Did you fall on your head?
I told you to stay away.
You did?
I forgot.
Why are you acting so weird?
(STAMMERS) I'm sorry. I
didn't sleep well last night.
Mmm-hmm.
Well, I just came
to feed my cat.
So if you're not
gonna leave, I am.
- I promised myself I'd stay away.
- (SIGHS)
That it would be safer that way.
But things have changed.
What are you talking about?
You know what? I don't care.
Just don't be here
when I get back.
Selina, wait.
I'm not Bruce.
- DR. THOMPKINS: Jim.
- Lee, now's not a good time.
DR. THOMPKINS:
Your uncle's autopsy.
Ballistics came back
negative. No match.
But there were microscopic tears
along the entry wound made postmortem.
What are you saying?
Someone removed the
bullet that killed your uncle
and replaced it
with another one.
It's an old mob trick
to cover up a murder.
- You're reaching, Lee.
- I don't think so.
And I think you
know what happened.
Listen to me, you need to drop
this. You could get yourself hurt.
You think I care
what happens to me?
I am sick of watching you destroy
people's lives and get away with it.
When I find out what you did,
I'm going to make sure you pay
for it. And I'm going to enjoy it.
Jim, hey.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Where's the riddle?
Me and Lucius took a crack at it,
but maybe you'll have better luck.
"You can see me, but
you cannot touch me.
"With the flick of a
switch, I enter your home,
"with another, I
leave you alone.
- "Where am I?"
- He's taunting us. If he kills James,
the press is gonna hand us
our asses on the 6:00 news.
Harvey, you're a genius.
Yeah, tell me
something I don't know.
I have a question. What
is this mysterious Court
that controls the levers
of power here in Gotham?
Alvarez, go to Channel 7!
Find out where Nygma's
broadcasting from.
Our dear Mayor's
head be blown to bits
- in order to keep their anonymity.
- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
(ED LAUGHING)
- KATHRYN: Are you watching the television?
- I am.
The Court cannot be exposed.
We would clean this up on our own,
but there are too many eyes watching.
However, this does afford
us an opportunity, James.
To prove my loyalty.
You want me to find
Nygma and bring him to you?
I understand this puts
you in a difficult position.
He's a cop killer.
He belongs in prison.
KATHRYN: If you decline,
this conversation will be our last.
The choice is yours.
That was The Court.
- If I hand him over, I'm in.
- They'll probably kill him.
If I don't, we'll never stop
them from destroying the city.
I know what you're
thinking, Aubrey.
That the police are gonna
somehow find you, rescue you.
But I gave the GCPD
every chance to save you.
But they're no match
for me! (LAUGHING)
We're both dead men.
You don't get it, do you?
The Court's isn't
gonna bargain with you.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
You underestimate me, Mr. James.
- Hello.
- Nygma.
Jim. I'm so sorry. We can't
be clogging up the lines.
I'm actually expecting
an important call.
JIM: You wanna know
who runs Gotham?
I have the answer.
Come by the GCPD.
I'll tell it to you.
Hmm. Yeah, I think
I'll pass on that.
Then you'll never
know the truth.
You think I told Barbara
everything I know?
You always were
clever, Jim. I respect that.
Empty out the GCPD.
I want it to just be
you and me. Alone.
Well, and this idiot with
the bomb around his neck.
(GRUNTS)
BULLOCK: You think he'll show?
JIM: The thing that drives
Nygma is also his weakness.
He'll be here.
You sound like every
man, woman and child
in Gotham isn't depending
on you to succeed.
Yeah, no pressure.
- Good luck, pal.
- Thanks.
Where's Ed?
That lunatic dropped
me off, sent me in alone.
- Get the bomb squad in here.
- Sit down and shut up.
Ed. It's just the
two of us in here.
ED: Just wanted to make
sure I wasn't walking into a trap.
Nah, uh-uh.
Sit down, Aubrey.
You said you had the
answer I was looking for, Jim.
It would be incredibly
disappointing if this was all a ruse.
More so for Mayor James.
Just tell him what he wants.
He talks too much.
(LAUGHS)
You should probably just
go ahead and blow him up.
MAYOR JAMES: I'll
have your badge, Gordon.
I'm not bluffing, Jim.
Neither am I.
What's the blast
radius on that thing?
Am I good here? Or should
I duck behind the desk?
I want the answer, Jim!
I kill him, I still walk out of
here with you as my hostage.
- (CLICKS)
- No. No!
- No!
- (DETONATOR BEEPING)
(RADIO FREQUENCY BUZZING)
Oh, come on.
There's a radio frequency
jamming the signal
between the detonator
and the bomb.
- How?
- Tabitha.
She's holds quite the
grudge against you.
She called me. Told me
how to disarm the bomb.
(CHUCKLES)
I'll admit, I didn't
see this coming.
But that doesn't
change anything.
I want to know who The Court is.
Or Aubrey dies.
Don't.
You wanna know who runs Gotham?
Then let Mayor James go.
Take a ride with me.
But if you pull that trigger,
you'll never get the
answer you're looking for.
You fool me once, Jim.
(CLICKS TONGUE) Shame on you.
You fool me twice!
Well, that's just
not gonna happen.
Then the riddle
will go unsolved.
Fine.
Let's go.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
SELINA: Let me
get this straight.
So, this limo pulls up,
literally out of nowhere,
and this creepy
lady tells you to get in
because "you could
be so much more."
And you did?
I had nowhere else to go.
So, where have you
been the last few months?
It's not important.
What matters is you
need to leave Gotham.
- Right away.
- Why?
Because the city
has been judged.
And something bad is going to...
(SCOFFS) Judged by who?
The people who took you?
Wait a minute. Your
clothes, your hair.
The way you talk.
Where is Bruce?
- Selina...
- What did you do to him?
He's fine. He's not in Gotham,
but nothing bad is
going to happen to him.
- Then where is he?
- It doesn't matter.
You just have to trust me. You
need to leave Gotham today.
Trust you?
- (SCOFFS) I don't even know you.
- Where are you going?
- To tell Alfred.
- Selina...
Now, let me go.
Selina, you can't tell anyone.
Then why the hell
did you tell me?
Because I care about you.
And if there's one person I
want to save, I want it to be you.
(CHUCKLES)
That's the difference
between you and Bruce Wayne.
He would try and save everyone.
You can pretend all you want.
But you will never be him.
You're nothing. You're
not even a real person.
You don't matter.
You're wrong about me.
I do matter.
- And I won't let you tell Alfred.
- Oh, yeah?
How are you gonna stop...
(SELINA SCREAMING)
Remember the night you
came over to Lee's for dinner?
It feels like a lifetime ago.
Leslie made fondue.
The wine was a Bordeaux.
Well aged. Smooth tannins.
Miss Kringle wore a
black dress with pink trim.
I tried like hell
to get out of it.
(ED CHUCKLES)
Lee insisted.
The truth is, I had a good time.
I considered you a friend.
I can sneak up on you
or be right in front of you
without you even knowing.
But when I reveal myself,
you will never be the same.
- What am I?
- I don't care, Ed.
Betrayal.
That's how every
friendship ends.
So, what good are
friends anyway?
Who are they?
The answer to your question.
Hello, Mr. Nygma.
I hear you've been
asking about us.
How do I know you're real?
Isn't that the point
of a good mystery?
You're never quite sure
what to believe until the end.
Gordon could've
put you up to this.
I assure you, Detective Gordon
had to be convinced to bring you here.
But let me put it like this.
That question Professor Strange
had you ask Bruce Wayne and
Lucius Fox last year at Indian Hill,
the one that has tortured you,
the one you'll never
be able to answer...
That answer is with me.
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
What now?
Get in.
And all your questions
will be answered.
You won't be needing the gun.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
You've made us proud,
Detective Gordon.
What are you
going to do with him?
A man with Nygma's intellect
could be quite useful to us.
I'm sure we'll find
something for him to do.
We'll be in touch.
(ALTERNATIVE ROCK PLAYING)
Good evening, Ms. Kean.
May I offer you a drink?
(BOTTLE SHATTERS)
Something went wrong.
Gordon took down Nygma
before he could find out
the truth about The Court.
Probably 'cause I told Gordon
how to disarm the bomb.
What?
Why?
You promised that when Nygma
handed over the underworld,
I would get to kill him.
Sealed it with a kiss, remember?
Don't you get it?
As long as The
Court is out there,
I'll never be in control!
Don't you mean, "We'll
never be in control"?
Seen it a thousand times.
Ambition. Power.
People can't help themselves.
She's changed, baby.
- When are you gonna see that?
- Shut up, Butch!
Move!
This is trouble.
It's good to be home.
FYI, I've been to Wayne
Manor. It's way cleaner.
You never said anything
about Fries being a part of this.
You're a little hot.
Maybe you need to cool off.
IVY: Oh, come on, you guys.
We're on the same
team now, remember?
A family?
(WEAPONS POWER DOWN)
Keep him away from me.
There's a question
mark on your face.
You can sleep in the freezer.
(TV PLAYING)
Hey, Pengy. Check it out.
Do not call me Pengy! My...
AKA Edward Nygma, was
apprehended by the GCPD
this afternoon after kidnapping
interim Mayor Aubrey James.
However, while en
route to Arkham Asylum...
Riddler.
He managed to escape police
custody and is now at large.
How long did he have
to think about that one?
Rest up, everyone.
Tomorrow is going
to be a busy day.
(CAT MEOWING)
(CONTINUES MEOWING)
I'd like to introduce our
newest member, James Gordon.
Welcome to The Court of Owls.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
English -SDH